clipsyndicate.com 2013-06-05

# Clip Syndicate

### » Information Privacy Practices

At ClipSyndicate, a service of Critical Mention, Inc., we take your privacy seriously. The following sets out how we collect, use and disclose your personal information. This information is gathered at registration, during your use of the service or otherwise in oral and written communications. We understand the importance of maintaining your trust and confidence in ClipSyndicate and we shall endeavor to treat the personal information you submit to us consistent with this policy.

### » Collection & Use of Personal Information

ClipSyndicate gathers information about you when you register for the service and when you use our product. We may also gather personal financial information in order to pay you your revenue share from advertising sold on your site. When you register online to use the ClipSyndicate service we require you to provide certain personal information about yourself, such as your name, address, e-mail address and telephone number. This information may also be submitted to ClipSyndicate in written form or via the telephone. ClipSyndicate uses this personal information in several ways:

* To enable ClipSyndicate to process, validate and verify registrations

* To deliver the appropriate ClipSyndicate service to you

* To assess and improve our services to you and to keep you informed about updates

* To advise you on your use of the ClipSyndicate services

* To make you aware of additional ClipSyndicate services that may be of interest to you

* To deliver targeted advertising in the ClipSyndicate network

* To invoice and deliver payment to individual registrants

ClipSyndicate delivers targeted advertising based upon personal information. This information is shared in a non-personally identifiable way with certain partners, such as ad serving companies to deliver ads based upon targeting criteria such as, demographics and geographics. We may also use aggregate information about our users to understand what area users visit most frequently and what information users access the most. This information helps us determine what is most beneficial for our users, and how we can continually create a better overall service for you. We may also use data anonymously in connection with the royalties payable to our content licensors.

In certain circumstances, your usage of the ClipSyndicate service and the information that you have retrieved may be reported to your employer or the registrant who pays for you to access the service. In such cases, this personal usage data will only be transferred to the registered party that pays for your access to this service. This is done to provide the registrant with information as to how the service is being used within its organization and for its internal billing and costing purposes.

### » Storage of Personal Information

The personal information that you provide to ClipSyndicate is held on our servers. We retain this information for so long as you are registered with us and for a reasonable period thereafter to close your account. We share this information within the Critical Mention group of companies and with certain approved partners. Except as described above, we will not knowingly disclose any of this personal data or information about use of the ClipSyndicate services to outside parties (other than our sub-contractors if required), except when you expressly consent or we believe the law requires it.

### » Information Sharing

We may share anonymous information with our business partners so that they too may understand how ClipSyndicate's customers use our services. This information is never shared in a manner so that individual users can be personally identified.

We may disclose information as reasonably necessary to:

* Satisfy any applicable law, regulation, legal process or enforceable government request

* Enforce applicable Terms of Service, including investigation of potential violations thereof

* Detect, prevent, or otherwise address fraud, security, or technical issues 

* Protect against imminent harm to the rights, property, or safety of ClipSyndicate, a service of Critical Mention, Inc. or its users as permitted by law.

We may also ask you for additional information, to be provided at your discretion, in an effort to deliver to you the best possible service experience. With your permission, we may also use provide your personal information to certain third parties in order for them to make you aware of their services that may be of interest to you. ClipSyndicate provides you with the opportunity to opt-in to these types of communications. If you choose to receive these types of communications at the time of registration, but later decide you no longer want to receive them from ClipSyndicate or if would like ClipSyndicate to cease providing your personal information to third parties, simply select the Administration area and under My Account select the opt-out box.

### » Updating Account Information

You have the right to ask ClipSyndicate at any time for a copy of your personal information that we hold. This information shall be provided on payment of an administration fee. ClipSyndicate allows you to change or correct certain of your personal information at any time. To do so, simply select the Administration area, and under My Account you will find opportunity for editing the information you have submitted.

We reserve the right to send you certain communications relating to the ClipSyndicate service such as service announcements, administrative messages, and newsletters that are considered part of your account, without offering you the opportunity to opt out of receiving them.

### » Cookies

To enhance your experience of the ClipSyndicate services, we use a feature on your internet browser called a "cookie." Cookies are small files that your web browser places on your computer's hard drive. We use cookies for remembering user names and passwords and preferences, tracking click-streams, and for load balancing. Because of our use of cookies, we can deliver faster service, update results, and provide a more personalized site experience. If you disable cookies in your browser, ClipSyndicate's services may not work properly.

### » Feedback

ClipSyndicate provides the opportunity for you to submit feedback. Any feedback that is submitted becomes the property of ClipSyndicate. We may use this feedback, such as success stories, for marketing purposes, or to contact you for further information.

### » Changes in Privacy Practices

If ClipSyndicate decides to change this privacy policy we will post those changes here so that you will always know what information we gather and how we might use that information.
